

# Sasi Dharan

**Enterprise Sales Account Executive** 

tellsasidharan@gmail.com +91-8220449349 Chennai, India

linkedin.com/in/sasi-dharan

I'm a creative business person with a **Get-it-done attitude** having **five years of experience** building new businesses in **SAAS**. I'm adept at solving complex business growth challenges with solid skills in time management and people skills. Currently, I'm looking for **challenging Enterprise sales roles** in promising teams to realize **mutual hyper-growth**. The message "Yes. Let's sign this" makes my

US Market

US Market

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Sales Manager(Account Executive) VWO(Wingify)

07/2022 - Present

\$30Mn ARR SAAS company for website conversion optimization

- Reported to Head of Sales
- Responsible for US-SouthEast Territory Sales. Carrying an annual target of \$600K.
- Generating own leads and collaborating with two SDRs for finding accounts and sketching prospecting strategies.

# **Account Executive**

#### Oorwin Labs

04/2021 - 05/2022

AI-Powered SaaS solutions to boost recruiter's productivity.

- Reported to Director of Sales
- Carried an annual target of \$450K. Overachieved monthly quota: Aug'21 - 155%, Oct'21 - 198%, Jan'22 - 220%
- Onboarded 5 Enterprise Customers from a new industry (non-staffing) and drove the product transformation.
- Trained a 3-member SDR team for outbound prospecting and sales qualification methodologies.

# Enterprise Business Manager Botminds Inc.

05/2019 - 04/2021

US/India Market

Botminds is for Intelligent Document Process Automation using AI and ML.

- Reported to CEO
- Closed 10+ enterprise deals resulting in a total annual revenue of 800K from US and Indian BFSI.
- Developed and owned the multi-touch outbound campaigns that increased the demo-setting rate by 5x.
- Closely worked with the leadership team to create impactful presentations, proposals and execute GTM strategies.
- Attended industry events and built relationships that generated over 100 qualified deals.

### **SKILLS**

The state of the s	1
Enterprise Business Prospecting	
SaaS Demo Presentation	
C-Suite Negotiation	
Go To Market Strategies	
Copywriting	
AI/MarTech Tech Sales Experience	

# **EDUCATION**

Mechanical Engineering Rajalakshmi Engineering College 08/2013 - 05/2017

# **INTERESTS**

Tradeshows Playstation Volunteering

Stock trading Video Making

Wordpress

#### **CAUSES**

Rescue animals from distress & life-threatening situations.

Being vegan for life and advocating animal rights.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Account Manager**

# **SnackExperts**

12/2017 - 01/2019

India Market

SnackExperts delivers unique preservative-free healthy evening snacks to 100+ offices.

#### Reported to CEO and Head of Sales

- End-to-End Sales Cycle Role. Managed a 4-member team responsible for more than 40 IT clients worth two crore INR in revenue.
- Built a new line of business with snack vending machines and led the selling of smartcard-based machines that resulted in closing 15 new enterprise clients.

# **Founder** EngineerJi

01/2014 - 10/2017

India Market

EngineerJi was a student-freelancing marketplace that helped startups to get gigs done at cheaper costs.

#### Achievements

 Built the online student freelance marketplace with more than 150 vetted student talents. Around 200 startup microprojects were carried out through the marketplace.

# **TESTIMONIALS**

Sasidharan has excellent selling and branding skills which will be invaluable for any growth team. He can be your next 10X talent for sure. "Arun Prakash(Head of Sales - SnackExperts)"

Its great to watch you closely, your creativity and your willingness to learn new things. You are an elephant catcher, go for it. "Gokul(CEO - Botminds Inc.)"